[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 54? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "9156.24",
      "options": [
        "9156.24",
        "9159.24",
        "9154.74",
        "9157.74"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 4? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "50.24",
      "options": [
        "50.24",
        "48.74",
        "53.24",
        "51.74"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 45? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "6358.5",
      "options": [
        "6357.0",
        "6358.5",
        "6360.0",
        "6361.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 36? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "4069.44",
      "options": [
        "4070.94",
        "4069.44",
        "4072.44",
        "4067.94"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 7? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "153.86",
      "options": [
        "155.36",
        "152.36",
        "153.86",
        "156.86"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 38? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "4534.16",
      "options": [
        "4532.66",
        "4535.66",
        "4537.16",
        "4534.16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 57? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "10201.86",
      "options": [
        "10201.86",
        "10200.36",
        "10203.36",
        "10204.86"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 49? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "7539.14",
      "options": [
        "7540.64",
        "7542.14",
        "7539.14",
        "7537.64"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 25? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "1962.5",
      "options": [
        "1964.0",
        "1965.5",
        "1962.5",
        "1961.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 27? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2289.06",
      "options": [
        "2287.56",
        "2289.06",
        "2290.56",
        "2292.06"
      ]
    }
]